[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Josef von Sternberg made this lady a star when he cast her as Lola-Lola in The Blue Angel.\nWho sang Men cluster to me like moths to a flame. And if they get burned, I know Im not to blame?", "correct_answer": "Marlene Dietrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary Pickford", "Theda Bara", "Clara Bow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the young, honest lawyer who won the case in the movie and novel The Rainmaker.", "correct_answer": "Rudy Baylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Ted Buckland", "Billy Flynn", "Sydney Carton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous male hip hop artist appears in Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "DMX", "incorrect_answers": ["Nas", "P. Diddy", "Slim Thug"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 71st Academy Awards in 1999, this 1998 film received the Academy Award for Best Picture.", "correct_answer": "Shakespeare in Love", "incorrect_answers": ["Elizabeth", "The Thin Red Line", "Saving Private Ryan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1960s ABC series do the characters attack, harass and wreak havoc on Field Marshal Rommels vaunted Afrika Korps?", "correct_answer": "The Rat Patrol", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mod Squad", "Gunsmoke", "M.A.S.H"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the first American-made motorcycle manufactured?", "correct_answer": "Springfield , Massachusetts", "incorrect_answers": ["Birmingham, Alabama", "Savannah, Georgia", "Kansas City, Missouri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Mike Myers and Graham Gordy  2008 movie The Love Guru\u201d stars Myers, Jessica Alba,  Justin Timberlake, Ben Kingsley and this diminutive former Mike Myers co-star.", "correct_answer": "Verne Troyer", "incorrect_answers": ["Jason Acuna", "Danny Woodburn", "Steve Delano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pi Day, the day which honors the mathematical constant \u03c0 (Pi), is celebrated on which date?", "correct_answer": "March 14", "incorrect_answers": ["August 25", "February 25", "January 14"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the first four planets of the Solar System in order of their distance from the Sun?", "correct_answer": "Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars, Venus, Earth, Mercury", "Jupiter, Venus, Mars, Earth", "Saturn, Pluto, Jupiter, Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She won the Worst Actress Razzies in 1982  for Butterfly and in 1983 for The Lonely Lady.", "correct_answer": "Pia Zadora", "incorrect_answers": ["Bo Derek", "Faye Dunaway", "Liza Minelli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prepare 1 1/2 oz gin, 2 tsp grapefruit juice, 1 tbsp maraschino liqueur.  Mix all ingredients and shake them with ice. Then strain into a cocktail glass. Add a sprig of mint.", "correct_answer": "Seventh Heaven", "incorrect_answers": ["Singapore Sling", "Silver Fizz", "Sangria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many natural satellites does Jupiter have?", "correct_answer": "63", "incorrect_answers": ["18", "56", "60"]}]